https://www.estruxture.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy1. Our Commitment to PrivacyeStruxture Data Centers Inc. and its affiliates (“eStruxture“, “we“, “us“) are committed to protecting the accuracy, privacy and security of your Personal Information (as defined below) which you may provide to us or we may obtain in the course of your relationship with us. This eStruxture privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy“) is a statement of principles and guidelines that describes the type of Personal Information we collect, the manner in which we do so and how we treat it, consistent with our commitment to respecting your online privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection of any Personal Information that you share with us.Our Privacy Policy is designed to comply with applicable privacy acts and applies to our company sales, our websites (the “Site“, currently at: https://www.eStruxture.com/), and all other manners or channels in which eStruxture collects and uses your Personal Information. Our Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.2. What is Personal Information?For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means all recorded information about an identifiable individual, with the exception of the names and business contact information of employees and services providers, when used for business communications. Personal information that is aggregated and cannot be associated with an identifiable individual is not considered to be your Personal Information. The types of Personal Information that we may collect from you from time to time include:Name, address, telephone numbers, email addresses, credit card information, government-issued identification, ID check, biometric information, video and photo images and your photograph for access card purposes.We do not collect, access or process any Personal Information that is stored by our customers in our data centers.3. How and why we collect Personal Information?We collect most of our information about you directly from you, with your consent for the purposes outlined below. We may also obtain Personal Information about you from third parties, with your consent. For example, for credit evaluation purposes, we may need to determine your creditworthiness through contact with an independent credit-reporting agency.We will not collect or use Personal Information for any other or new purpose without obtaining consent, unless required or authorized by law.We generally collect Personal Information for the following purposes:Contact information: We collect Personal Information to establish, develop and preserve our business relationships with customers and other individuals with whom we deal with. We will usually collect your name, address, phone number(s) and email address, as well as other account and payment information, including information pertaining to your use of our products and services when you register for our services in order to create, establish and administer your account, to provide services, and to respond to inquiries. We will also use Personal Information to establish or verify the eligibility and credit of persons that use, or intend to use, one or more of the products or services we offer.Security and accuracy: We use Personal Information to authenticate the identity of our customers, for the administration of access to our facilities, for the security and protection of our operations, to preserve the privacy of our customers contacting us by telephone, electronic means or otherwise and to ensure our records are accurate in order to protect our customers and eStruxture from error and fraud.Management and quality: We collect Personal Information for internal training and quality assurance purposes, for audit purposes and to manage our businesses and ensure the efficiency, reliability and security of our systems and networks.Customer Service: From time to time we may also use Personal Information to conduct surveys on the quality of our products, services or customer service, to provide our customers with offers for additional products and services that we feel may be of interest to our customers or to provide personalized products and services as well as product recommendations and to understand and assess the interests, wants and changing needs of customers with a view to improving our products and services and developing new ones.Human Resources: If you have applied for employment with eStruxture, the Personal Information submitted with your job application will be used for recruitment and other customary human resources purposes. For example, we may send you information about new job opportunities within eStruxture as well as other career development resources.We do not sell or rent our customers’ Personal Information to any other party. However, we may share some of your Personal Information in the normal course of business within our corporate family or we may transfer your Personal Information to third party service providers who assist us in serving you, such as vendors, suppliers and agents. Our service providers may be located outside of Canada and may be required to disclose Personal Information under the laws of their jurisdiction.4. Information Collected from Your Use of the SiteTo ensure our Site is optimized for ease of use, or for future communications, we or our service provider(s) may use cookies to collect standard Internet log information about how and when you use the Site. This information may include but, not be limited to, your IP address and location data, weblogs, time, date, your language preferences, browser used, referring web addresses, other communication data, searches conducted, pages visited, etc.Our email marketing communications may contain a single, campaign-unique “web beacon pixel” to tell us whether our emails are opened and combined with other technology verify any clicks through to links within the email. We may use this information for purposes including determining which of our emails are more interesting to you and to query whether users who do not open our emails wish to continue receiving them. The pixel will be deleted when you delete the email. If you do not wish the pixel to be downloaded to your device, through your email account, you can opt to not download images from us.You may also choose not to click links in the email marketing communications that we send you. This information may be connected to your personal identity.5. ConsentWe will collect, use or disclose your Personal Information with your knowledge and consent, including as set out in this Privacy Policy, except where otherwise required or permitted by law. The method of obtaining consent depends on the circumstances and may be oral or written, express or implied. By using the Site, or by providing your Personal Information to us, you acknowledge and consent to the use of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.The law permits or requires that we collect, use or share your Personal Information in certain circumstances without your consent, including, for example, to investigate a breach of an agreement or a law or in response to a search warrant, or to investigate or deter fraud. In addition, we may be involved in the sale or transfer of some or all of our business. As part of that sale or transfer, we may disclose your Personal Information to the acquiring organization but will require the acquiring organization to agree to protect the privacy of your Personal Information in a manner that is similar to this Privacy Policy.You may change or withdraw your consent at any time, on reasonable notice, subject to legal or contractual restrictions. In order to change or withdraw your consent, please refer to the Contacting Us section below.6. Where is your Personal Information stored?Your Personal Information is stored in secured locations and on servers controlled by us, located solely within our offices and data centres within Canada.7. RetentionPersonal information will be retained only as long as necessary for the fulfilment of the purposes for which it was collected and for which consent was received, unless otherwise required by law. Personal information that is no longer required to fulfil the identified purposes might be destroyed, erased or made anonymous.8. How can you access your Personal Information?Upon written request, subject to certain exceptions, we will inform you of the existence, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information and will give you access to that information. We keep your information for the time we are providing you with a service, and for a reasonable time thereafter. For access to your Personal Information, please refer to the Contacting Us section below.9. How do we protect your Personal Information?We make commercially reasonable efforts to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of Personal Information under our control. Our security policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary.We employ administrative, contractual and technological safeguards to protect your information. For example, only authorized employees and suppliers have access to Personal Information of representatives of our customers and visitors of our facilities. Where information is sent to a third party for processing, we try to ensure that such service providers may only use the information for the limited purposes for which it was disclosed and are required to keep the information secure. Moreover, we operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems.10. Notice to the Data Subjects of Our CustomersIf you have provided Personal Information to our customers, or to customers of eStruxture affiliates, who are using eStruxture’s information technology services to store or otherwise process your Personal Information, all such Personal Information on our systems is provided and controlled by our customers who are the data controllers under applicable data protection law. eStruxture will not process that Personal Information and is not a “processor“, as such term is defined in certain data protection laws. The customers remain responsible for the Personal Information they collect and process and are not discharged of their obligations to comply with applicable data protection laws.eStruxture has no direct relationship with the individuals whose Personal Information is processed by our customers. If your Personal Information is on our systems as a result of you having provided it to one of our customers and would no longer like to be contacted by that customer, or you wish to exercise any other data protection rights, please contact that customer directly.If you would like more information on how your Personal Information will be processed and protected, as well as your rights in relation to that Personal Information, please refer to the privacy policy of the customer to which you provided your Personal Information. If you ask us to delete your Personal Information, we will tell our customer about this request.11. Contacting UsIf you have any questions, concerns, or wish to withdraw your consent, please contact us at:eStruxture Data Centers Inc.
800 rue Square-Victoria, SS1
Montreal, Quebec, H4Z 1A1
Phone: 1-514-369-2209
Toll-Free: 1-888-369-2209
Email : support@eStruxture.com12. AssignmentYou consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to a third-party acquirer of eStruxture’s business.13. Changes to This PolicyWe reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time in order to accommodate changes in our services, changes in technology, and legal developments. Each time you submit Personal Information or use our services, you agree to be bound by the then current terms of the Privacy Policy.14. LanguageThe parties have expressly requested and required that this Agreement and all other related documents be drawn up in the English language. Les parties conviennent et exigent expressément que ce Contrat et tous les documents qui s’y rapportent soient rédigés en anglais.Please note that both the English and French versions of our Privacy Policy have equal legal value.This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 2018. Cookie ConsentWe use cookies on our website. By continuing to use our website, you agree to the Privacy Policy.
